Joe Hollenbach

Software Engineer

github.com/justjoe19

linkedin.com/in/joe-hollenbach

joe-h.netflify.app

Summary

- Experience with Python, Java, Django, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, and React
- Experience with Mac and PC troubleshooting and repair
- · Experience with networking
- Job history of management and leadership experience

Skills

HTML; CSS; Javascript; Python; Java;
Web Development; SQL; Node.js; Django;
MongoDB; MySQL; Version Control; GitHub;
Bash; Unix; Linux; Networking; Bootstrap
Responsive Web Design; Cloud Computing;
Hardware and Software Troubleshooting;
Virtualization; Computer Repair;
Technical Support; User Interface Design;
Front-End Development;
Object-Oriented Programming

Work Experience

December 2021 - present

Mishawaka, IN

Apple, Inc. - Pro

- Perform face-to-face technical support for iPhone, iPad, Apple Watch, and Mac
- Provide customers with issue troubleshooting, product diagnosis and potential solutions
- Leader in product sales, product knowledge, and customer satisfaction

January 2019 - June 2021

Mishawaka, IN

Jordan Auto Group - Acquisitions Manager

- In charge of purchasing and pricing up to 250vehicle inventory
- Merchandise and advertise each vehicle online using web application tools
- Oversee and support appraisal and reconditioning processes for each vehicle

Education

Jan 2022 - Mar 2024

South Bend, IN

Associate of Applied Science - Software Development

Ivy Tech Community College

Oct 2020 - Dec 2022

South Bend, IN

Technical Certificate in Software Development

Ivy Tech Community College

Certifications

· A+ Certification

CompTIA, March 2024

Software Application Developer Certificate
 Ivy Tech Community College, May 2023

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner
 Amazon Web Services, May 2023

· PC Pro Certification

TestOut Corporation, June 2021